{
  "response_code": 0,
  "results": [
    {
      "category": "Science%3A%20Animals",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Which%20animal%20is%20known%20for%20its%20stripes%20and%20is%20associated%20with%20jungles%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Tiger",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Giraffe",
        "Zebra",
        "Cheetah"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Science%3A%20Animals",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What%20is%20the%20largest%20land%20mammal%20in%20the%20world%3F",
      "correct_answer": "African%20Elephant",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Giraffe",
        "Hippopotamus",
        "White%20Rhinoceros"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Science%3A%20Animals",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Which%20bird%20is%20known%20for%20its%20long%20neck%20and%20ability%20to%20fly%20great%20distances%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Albatross",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Flamingo",
        "Ostrich",
        "Penguin"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Science%3A%20Animals",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What%20is%20the%20only%20flying%20mammal%20in%20the%20world%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Bat",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Squirrel",
        "Flying%20Fox",
        "Marmoset"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Science%3A%20Animals",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Which%20of%20the%20following%20animals%20is%20venomous%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Black%20Mamba",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "King%20Cobra",
        "Boa%20Constrictor",
        "Python"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Science%3A%20Animals",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What%20is%20the%20largest%20species%20of%20bear%20in%20the%20world%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Polar%20Bear",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Brown%20Bear",
        "Black%20Bear",
        "Sloth%20Bear"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Science%3A%20Animals",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Which%20animal%20is%20known%20for%20its%20ability%20to%20change%20color%20to%20blend%20with%20its%20environment%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Chameleon",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Frog",
        "Gecko",
        "Octopus"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Science%3A%20Animals",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What%20is%20the%20fastest%20land%20animal%20in%20the%20world%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Cheetah",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Lion",
        "Gazelle",
        "Leopard"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Science%3A%20Animals",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Which%20animal%20is%20known%20for%20its%20long%20tongue%20and%20ability%20to%20capture%20insects%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Anteater",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Armadillo",
        "Pangolin",
        "Aardvark"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Science%3A%20Animals",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What%20is%20the%20world%27s%20largest%20species%20of%20shark%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Whale%20Shark",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Great%20White%20Shark",
        "Hammerhead%20Shark",
        "Tiger%20Shark"
      ]
    }
  ]
}
